(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Sharon Carter wanted to take a pottery class.
She didn't want to go alone.
She invited her husband to go with her.
I don't want to do that, said Mr.
Carter.
Pottery is for girls.
This made Sharon very angry.
She could not believe he said that.
That's a sexist thing to say, yelled Sharon.
She argued with him for hours.
Mr. Carter was tired of fighting.
He agreed to go just to shut Sharon
up.
Their first class went very well.
Mr. Carter was really good at making pots.
The instructors loved him.
You are very talented, they all said.
Mr. Carter went to pottery class every week
after that.
He loved it!